Guide to the Donald Jay Grout papers,1929-2002.
Grout, Donald Jay papers
- Series III. History of Western Music
  - Material related to the second (1973) and third (1980) editions
    - Notes, articles, drafts, comments, suggestions, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Notes and articles, 1968-1970 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Notes and articles, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous material, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Notes, articles, drafts, comments, suggestions, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Notes, comments, suggestions, drafts, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Notes and articles, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Notes, comments, suggestions, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Notes and drafts, 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Miscellaneous leftovers - begun 1960", 1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Polish music, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Notes and drafts, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Comments and articles, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Notes and revisions, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Notes and articles, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Opinions and comments, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Opinions and comments, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Opinions and comments, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Corrections and suggestions received, 1961-1971, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Revisions divided into folders, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 23-44)
    - List of scores and recordings, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - for "The Music Review", 1975 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Notes, drafts, and other material, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Longyear's annotations, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Facenda, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Worksheets, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Notes and comments, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - After Webern (chapter XX), 1972 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Comments on last edition, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Galleys
    - Printers' proofs, n.d. (Box 29)
    - Grout's page and first set, n.d. (Box 30)
    - Editorial: Frontispiece-XIII, n.d. (Box 31)
    - Editorial: XIV - Index, n.d. (Box 32)
    - Editorial, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous galleys, n.d. (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous galleys, unbound copy (corrected), n.d. (Box 35)
    - Illustrations and photos, numbered illustrations, music, n.d. (Box 36)
    - Chapters I-VI, n.d. (Box 37)
    - Chapters VII-XII, n.d. (Box 38)
    - Chapters XIII-end, n.d. (Box 39)
    - Page proofs, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    - Annotated volume 1960 edition, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
    - Page proofs, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
    - Page proofs, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Galleys, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 3-5)
- Series IV. The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti
  - Eraclea
    Vol. I of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti.
    - Programs, synopsis, timings sent to Royal College of Music, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Act I (before intermission) vocal score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Act II (omissions) vocal score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Act III (after intermission) vocal score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Sinfonia Act I score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Act II score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Act III score, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Critical notes Act I, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Critical notes Act II, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Critical notes Act III, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Libretto prepared by Edward Swenson, April 1968 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Completely edited libretto, Napoli 1700 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Introduction, style sheet, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous leftovers, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Eraclea at Cornell, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Papers for Z. Lissa Festschrift, May 1971 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Transparencies for orchestral scores by Gaynor Grey Jones '69, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
    - Violins, Act I (12 score copies), n.d. (Box 20)
    - Violins, Act II (12 score copies), n.d. (Box 20)
    - Violins, Act III (8 score copies), n.d. (Box 20)
    - Violins, Act III (4 score copies), n.d. (Box 21)
    - Basses, Act I, II, III (7 copies each), n.d. (Box 21)
    - Flutes (2 copies), n.d. (Box 21)
    - Oboes (2 copies), n.d. (Box 21)
    - Trumpets (2 copies)., n.d. (Box 21)
    - Cambridge (Magdalen College Lib.), Pepys Ms. 1807 - A. Scarlatti, 46 arie from L'Eraclea (I), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Cambridge (Magdalen College Lib.), Pepys Ms. 1807 - A. Scarlatti, 46 arie from L'Eraclea (II), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Vienna (Nat. Bibl.), SA.68.6.17 - A. Scarlatti, Sinfonia+Arias from L'Eraclea, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Eraclea, Introduction, libretto (excerpts), synopsis, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 15a)
    - Library of Congress, M48S.9195 - Eraclea, libretto (Venice, 1696) (Box 67, Folder 15b)
    - A. Scarlatti, Eraclea, n.d. (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - A. Scarlatti, Eraclea (passages cut from 1970 performance at Cornell), n.d. (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Dresden (Sächsische Landesbibliothek), Mus 1/F/39,1 - A. Scarlatti, scene buffe dell' Eraclea [recitatives, arias, duets] (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Rome (S. Cecilia), Carv. 5618 - L'Eraclea, libretto [not Scarlatti's] (Genoa, 1705?) (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Marco Attilio Regolo
    Vol. II of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti.
    - Partial score (photo copies), n.d. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Library of Congress, M1500.S28.A7 - A. Scarlatti, Attilio Regolo(Act I), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Library of Congress, M1500.S28.A7 - A. Scarlatti, Attilio Regolo(Act II), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Library of Congress, M1500.S28.A7 - A. Scarlatti, Attilio Regolo(Act III), 1912 copy of British Museum manuscript (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Library of Congress, M1505S38A.6 - A. Scarlatti, L'Attilio Regolo (fragments), n.d. (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), Litt. Q16.28 - A Scarlatti, Two Duets from M. Attilio Regolo, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Cambridge (Fitzwilliam Museum), Mus. Ms 24-E-9 - A. Scarlatti, M. Attilio Regolo(arias, Act I), n.d. (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Cambridge (Fitzwilliam Museum), Mus. Ms 24-E-9 - A. Scarlatti, M. Attilio Regolo(arias, Act II), n.d. (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Cambridge (Fitzwilliam Museum), Mus. Ms 24-E-9 - A. Scarlatti, M. Attilio Regolo(arias, Act III) + letter concerning purchase of this work, A. Scarlatti's Dafne e Galatea, and a work by Franc. Scarlatti (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Griselda
    Vol. III of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti.
    - Notes, tables, etc.; also, notes from British Museum on other scores, 1956 - 1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Zeno's Griselda, June 1967 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Index of Paris mss., 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Worksheets Introduction, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Lines of L (not set to music, or at least not crossed out in A.), 1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Notes for libretto article, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Notes for articles, etc., 1967 - 1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Early notes, 1967 - 1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Documents from Mrs. Kirkendale, Nov. 1969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Paper: "Original Version of Griselda" carbon and mss., October 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence related to Scarlatti article for Westrup volume, 1970 - 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Appendix - final version, January 1974 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - First drafts - superseded, February 1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Carbons, etc. of final versions, February 1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous notes, January - February 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Appendix first draft, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Incipits of Arias - by computer, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Version for Berkeley, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Notes, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Music examples, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Critical notes, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Libretto and some appendix, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Act I text, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Act II text, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Act III text, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Act I music, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Act II music, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Appendix, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Editor's mss. score, introduction to page 132, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Editor's mss. score, pages 133-271, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Editor's mss. score, pages 272-407, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Editor's mss. score, pages 408-547, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Galley, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Library of Congress, M1500.S28G5 case - A. Scarlatti, arias from Griselda, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek 19,640 - A. Scarlatti, La Griselda (Act I), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek 19,640 - A. Scarlatti, La Griselda (Act II), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Berlin Staatsbibliothek 19,640 - A. Scarlatti, La Griselda (Act III), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3894 - A. Scarlatti, La Griselda (Act I), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3894 - A. Scarlatti, La Griselda (Act II), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3894 - A. Scarlatti, La Griselda (Act III), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Library of Congress, M48S.2866 - La Griselda, libretto (Venice, 1701) (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Parma (Biblioteca del conservatorio di musica "A Boito"), 62845 - La Griselda, libretto (Livorno 1704) (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Modena (Bibl. Est.), 83. H 3.6 - La Griselda, libretto (Pavia 1710) (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - British Museum, 163.g.15 - La Griselda, libretto (London, Ward, 1721) (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Bologna (Cons. Bibl.) 6560 - Griselda, libretto (Florence, 1703) (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Milan (Braidense), Racc. Dramm. 1685 - Griselda, libretto (Verona, 1703) (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.) - Griselda, libretto (Napoli, 1706) (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Bologna (Bibl. Univ.), Caps. 99.30, Scenica VII.40 - La virtù nel trionfo, o sia la Griselda(Ferrara, 1708) (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Bologna (Cons. Bibl.) 55 - La Griselda, libretto (Piacenza, 1708) (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Bologna (Bibl. Univ.), Aula V, Tab.I, FIII, vol.35/1-8 - La virtù nel trionfo, o sia la Griselda(Bologna, 1711) (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Library of Congress, ML48.S7331 (=Schatz 7331) - La virtù nel cimento [=Griselda], Libretto (Mantova, 1717) (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Modena (Bibl. Est.) 83.D.24.3 - Griselda, libretto (Milano, 1718) (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Milano (Braidense) Racc. Dramm. 1684 - Griselda, libretto (Padua, 1719) (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Milano (Braidense) Racc. Dramm. 3126 - Griselda, libretto (Venezia, 1720) (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Rome (S. Cecilia), Carv 7807 - Griselda, libretto (Florence, 1722) (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Milano (Braidense) Racc. Dramm. 2514 - Griselda, libretto (Vienna, 1725) (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Library of Congress ML49A22.3 - Griselda, libretto by Zeno (Venice, 1744) [identical, except for pagination and details of typography, with the edition of Orléans, Vol II (1785), pp. 137-216] (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - The Faithful Princess
    Vol. IV of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti.
    - Mss. score through page 102, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Mss. score pages 103-215, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Mss. score pages 216-end, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Libretto 5116 (photocopy), Naples 1710 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Introduction notes, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Proofs and mss. critical notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Mss. libretto, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Corrections, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Libretto galleys, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Introduction mss. and carbon, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous material (notes, suggestions), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Table and summary of contents, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Two sets of galley scores, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Massimo Pupieno
    Vol. V of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti.
    - Score (photocopy), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Score (photocopy), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Contents, introduction, libretto translations, critical notes, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Introduction, contents, footnotes (photocopies), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Critical notes (photocopies), n.d. (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Florence (Bibl. del Cons.), melodrammi 2321.2 - Massimo Pupieno(Florence, 1691), 1697 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Florence (Bibl. del Cons.), 1.00x.95(4) - Massimo Pupieno(Livorno, 1697) (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Montecassino, 126 c.40 - A. Scarlatti, Massimo Pupieno, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), Ms. Litt. 15,321 - A. Scarlatti, 29 Arie from Massimo Puppieno and other operas (?) (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - A. Scarlatti, Massimo Pupieno - Complete Transcription and Revisionsbericht (Act I), 1968 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - A. Scarlatti, Massimo Pupieno - Complete Transcription and Revisionsbericht (Act II), 1968 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - A. Scarlatti, Massimo Pupieno - Complete Transcription and Revisionsbericht (Act III), 1968 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Library of Congress, M48S7727 (=Schatz 7727) - Massimo Puppieno, libretto [Venice 1685 (?)] (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - La caduta de'Decemviri
    Vol. VI of The Operas of Alessandro Scarlatti.
    - Suggestions for Ms. Williams for La Caduta, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Vassar - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act I, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Vassar - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act II, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Vassar - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act III, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Montréal (Cons. de musique) - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act I, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Montréal (Cons. de musique)- Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act II, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Montréal (Cons. de musique) - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act III, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 6.7.21 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act I, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 6.7.21 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act II, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 6.7.21 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La caduta de' Decemviri, Act III, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - British Museum, Ms. 14, 170 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act I, 1698 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - British Museum, Ms. 14, 170 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act II, 1698 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - British Museum, Ms. 14, 170 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act III, 1698 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.27 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act I, 1697 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.27 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act II, 1697 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms. 32.2.27 - Ms. of A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act III, 1697 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), B-BR/MsII 3967 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act I, 1700 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), B-BR/MsII 3967 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act II, 1700 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique), B-BR/MsII 3967 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri, Act III, 1700 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Dresden (Sächsische Landesbibliothek), Mus.Ms. 7F39.2 ff72-98 (=pages 143-195) - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri(excerpt), 1700 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Naples (Bibl. di Cons.), Ms. 6.7.18-20 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri (Act I), n.d. (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Naples (Bibl. di Cons.), Ms. 6.7.18-20 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri (Act II), n.d. (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Naples (Bibl. di Cons.), Ms. 6.7.18-20 - A. Scarlatti, La Caduta de' Decemviri (Act III), n.d. (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Critical notes for La Caduta de' Decemviri, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.) 6004 - La Caduta de' Decemviri, libretto (Naples 1697) (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Florence (Biblioteca Marucelliana) - La caduta de' Decemviri, libretto (Livorno, 1699) (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Modena (Bibl. Est.), 83 H 31/12 - La Caduta de' Decemviri, libretto (Reggio 1699) (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.) 6005 - La Caduta de' Decemviri, libretto (Florence 1700) (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Parma (Biblioteca del conservatorio di musica "A Boito") - La caduta de' Decemviri, libretto (Parma 1701) (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Brussels (Cons. Royal de musique) - La caduta de' Decemviri, libretto (Siena 1704) (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Unpublished manuscript scores, libretti and notes.
    by A. Scarlatti and contemporaries
    - U.C.L.A. - Unidentified arias (Bononcini's Griselda?), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Univ. of Washington, Seattle, Ms. Uncat. 650 - Pasquini, arias from Tessalonica, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3000 - Bernardo Pasquini, L'Alcasta (Act I), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3000 - Bernardo Pasquini, L'Alcasta (Act II), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3000 - Bernardo Pasquini, L'Alcasta (Act III), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Gräflich Schönbornsche Musikbibliothek - B. Pasquini, Il Lisimaco (Act I), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Gräflich Schönbornsche Musikbibliothek - B. Pasquini, Il Lisimaco (Act II), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Gräflich Schönbornsche Musikbibliothek - B. Pasquini, Il Lisimaco (Act III), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Univ. of Washington, Seattle, Ms. Uncat. 652 - A. Scarlatti, arias from Tutto il Mal.../B. Pasquini, arias from Il Lisimacho, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Vienna (Nat. Bibl.), Hs 18,904 - Intermedio: Il Giudice di Villa (Pederzuoli?), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Naples (Bibl. di Cons.), Ms 206386 - D. Sarri, La Ginevra, principessa di Scozia (Act I), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 206386 - D. Sarri, La Ginevra, principessa di Scozia (Act II), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), Ms 206386 - D. Sarri, La Ginevra, principessa di Scozia (Act III), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Library of Congress, M1500.S28G5 case - Arias from operas by composers more or less contemporary with Scarlatti, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - British Museum, Ms. 34,298 I (arias by A. Scarlatti), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - British Museum, Ms. 34,298 II (arias by F. Gasparini), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - British Museum, Ms. 34,298 III (arias by A. Scarlatti, F. Mancini), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 31,488 I (includes A. Scarlatti, Aria from Rosaura), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 31,488 II (Scarlatti, Stradella), n.d. (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Rochester (Sibley Library), Vault M1620 S286 Ca. I (A. Scarlatti, collected arias), n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Rochester (Sibley Library), Vault M1620 S286 Ca. II (A. Scarlatti, collected arias), n.d. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Rochester (Sibley Library), Vault M1620 S286 Ca. III (A. Scarlatti, collected arias), n.d. (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - I: FC D.886 (A. Scarlatti - "7 cantate con basso numerato," "5 arie con basso numerato ed archi", n.d. (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Dresden, Sächsische Landesbibliothek, Mus. 1 F39, 1 (scene buffe from various Italian operas) (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Dresden, Sächsische Landesbibliothek, Mus. 1 F39, 2 (scene buffe from operas by A. Scarlatti and others) (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Various libretti, n.d. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Cambise, libretto (Naples, 1719) (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Il Ciro, libretto (Rome, 1712) (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), 34.5.2 (Hanley No. 161) - A. Scarlatti, Da sventura à sventura, cantata (realization of figured bass by the composer), n.d. (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms.D.11, 897 - A. Scarlatti, Il figlio delle selve (Act I), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms.D.11, 897 - A. Scarlatti, Il figlio delle selve (Act II), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Paris (Bibl. du Cons.), Ms.D.11, 897 - A. Scarlatti, Il figlio delle selve (Act III), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6414 - Il Figlio delle selve, libretto (Rome, 1708) (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6414 - Il Figlio delle selve, libretto (Bologna, 1718) (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6415 - Il Figlio delle selve, libretto (Florence, 1720) (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4144 - A. Scarlatti, 42 arie from Il Flavio Cuniberto (I), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4144 - A. Scarlatti, 42 arie from Il Flavio Cuniberto (II), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4144 - A. Scarlatti, 42 arie from Il Flavio Cuniberto (III), n.d. (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Münster (Santini Collection), Hs. 3950 - A. Scarlatti, 16 arie from Il Flavio Cuniberto, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4143 - A. Scarlatti, aria "Mora pera vuò severa vendicarmi" from Il Flavio Cuniberto (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Rome (Bibl. Vat.), Barb. Lat. 4158 - A. Scarlatti, aria "Farfalletta intorno al lume" from Il Flavio Cuniberto, n.d. (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6442 - Flavio Cuniberto, libretto (Florence, 1697) (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Flavio Cuniberto, libretto (Florence, 1702) (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Flavio Cuniberto, libretto (Florence, 1702) (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Milano (Braidense) - Flavio Cuniberto, libretto (Lucca, 1706) (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 5123 - La forza della fedeltà, libretto (Fano, 1716) (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.), Lib. 6469 - La forza della fedeltà, libretto (Florence, 1711) (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Brussels (Bibl. del Cons.), K. 2347 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Act I), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Brussels (Bibl. del Cons.), K. 2347 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Act II), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Brussels (Bibl. del Cons.), K. 2347 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Act III), n.d. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Modena (Bibl. Est.), Ms. Mus. F.1055 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Act I), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Modena (Bibl. Est.), Ms. Mus. F.1055 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Act II), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Modena (Bibl. Est.), Ms. Mus. F.1055 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Act III), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Venice (Bibl. Marc.), Ms IV, 375 (=9899) - A. Scarlatti, Eurillo (=Gli equivoci nel sembiante), n.d. (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Vienna (Nat. Bibl.), Hs. 18,904 - A. Scarlatti, Amor non vuol inganni (=Gli equivoci nel sembiante), Act I, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Rome (S. Cecilia), Mss 308 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Bologna (Civ. Mus.) BB320 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - British Museum, Ms. Add. 31,515 fol. 18b-21b - A. Scarlatti, arias from Gli equivoci nel sembiante, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), ms. 33.5.16 - A. Scarlatti, aria "Già che amor non vuol desistere" from Gli equivoci nel sembiante, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), ms. 33.5.17 - A. Scarlatti, aria "Onde ferro fiamma" from Gli equivoci nel sembiante (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Naples (Bibl. del Cons.), ms. 60.1.54 - A. Scarlatti, Gli equivoci nel sembiante (20 arie e duetti indicati come autore ignoto) (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Venice (Bibl. Marc.), Ms. ItIV, 1911 (=10658) - A. Scarlatti, aria from Eurillo, n.d. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - L'errore innocente overro Gli equivoci nel sembiante, libretto (Bologna, 1679) (Box 68, Folder 13)